uchastings.edu 2019-07-02

# Privacy Policy Notice - UC Hastings College of the Law

The University of California Hastings College of the Law (UC Hastings) has created this privacy notice to explain how we use information that you may provide while visiting our website and to demonstrate our firm commitment to Internet privacy. UC Hastings reserves the right to make changes to its privacy policy without notice. We encourage you to check this page when revisiting this website. The following discloses our information gathering practices for this website. The type and amount of information received depends on how you use the site.

Once admitted and enrolled, UC Hastings students are protected by the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA).

## What information we gather during your visit

_Information we gather:_

We automatically collect certain information from you when you visit [www.uchastings.edu](http://www.uchastings.edu/).  This data is used in conjunction with Google Analytics to gather metrics on site usage including geographic location of visitors, pathways navigated through the website, and which portion of our audience is internal to the UC Hastings network. The information we collect is not linked to anything that identifies you as an individual.  Your session will be tracked but you will remain anonymous as a user. As part of Google Analytics, we also gather device and browser-related information. By using this website, you consent to the processing of your data by Google for the aforementioned purposes. Please visit [Google Analytics’ terms of service](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and [Google’s privacy policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) for more information.

_Information you may provide:_

There are designated forms, services and tools throughout this website for visitors to voluntarily provide personal information (name, phone number, email address, etc.) in exchange for information about our degree programs, events or other initiatives. By providing this information, you consent to receive marketing communications from the law school by phone, email or other advertising. Users can opt out of these communications at any time by contacting [helpdesk@uchastings.edu](mailto:helpdesk@uchastings.edu).  This information is not sold to or shared with third parties unless required in response to legal processes.

## How we use your information

We use this information on an aggregate basis to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of the site to our visitors. For example, we use this information to track which pages are most popular among visitors.

## With whom we share your information

Information we gather may also be shared with campus constituents to improve programs, outreach, and other campus initiatives. Additionally, metrics may be shared with vendors to improve communications related to these activities.

## Cookies and other collection technologies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. We use cookies on our site to personalize and customize the experience of our visitors and to support some necessary functions. We also use cookies to better understand how our visitors use our site. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. For more information on how to modify your browser settings to block or filter cookies, see <http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/>. However, please note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at this and on other sites throughout the Internet may not be complete.

No method of transmitting over the internet or storing electronic data is 100% secure, but this site has measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information that is under our control.

## Social Media Presence

If you share our content through social media, such as liking us on Facebook or tweeting about us on Twitter, those social networks will record that you have done so and may set a cookie for this purpose.

If you wish to opt-out of any of these social interactions please refer to the specific social media platform for instructions on how to do so.

## External Website Links

From time-to-time, we will link to external websites that we neither own nor control. This site contains hypertext links to other sites. UC Hastings is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website they visit. This privacystatement applies solely to this website.

## Special Notice for EU Residents

If you are located within the European Economic Area (European Union, Norway, Liechtenstein, and Iceland), we acknowledge the rights granted to you under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

These rights may include:

  1. Right to access your information held by us
  2. Right to correct inaccurate or incorrect information about you
  3. Right to the erasure of your information when it is no longer necessary for us to retain it
  4. Right to restrict processing of your personal information in specific situations
  5. Right to object to processing your information, including sending you communications that may be considered direct-marketing materials
  6. Right to object to automated decision-making and profiling, where applicable
  7. Right to complain to a supervisory authority in your jurisdiction within the EU

Please contact us with any questions, concerns, or if you wish to exercise any of these rights: [traynume@uchastings.edu](mailto:traynume@uchastings.edu)

## Contact Information

If you have questions about our privacy notice or the privacy practices it describes, please contact the [General Counsel’s Office.](https://www.uchastings.edu/people/leo-martinez/)
